# </salt>

School of applied technology



### Darko Jecinac

After many years of hobby coding and big love for technology, I've decided to make it a professional career. I found </Salt> the prestigious coding Bootcamp in my current home city of Stockholm and this is where my professional fullstack developer journey started.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

#### General

JavaScript, TypeScript

### Backend

NodeJS, Yarn, ExpressJS REST, HTTP, JSON, Ajax GraphQL, MongoDB, Mongoose, PostgreSQL

#### Frontend

React, Redux, Next, React Native Webpack, HTML5, jQuery CSS/SASS/Styled Components

### Tools and technologies

Visual Studio Code, Atom
Pug, EJS,
Mocha, Jest
Docker
Git, GitHub
AWS
Cloud Platforms (MongoDB Atlas,
ElephantSQL, Netlify, Heroku,
Contentful)
TDD
Agile work methods

# Links LinkedIn

GitHub

#### Languages

English - fluent
Swedish - intermediate
Serbo-Croatian - fluent

### **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

## Full Stack JavaScript - School of Applied Technology </salt>

Sep 2020 - Dec 2020 Intensive three month training program for full stack web development with a focus on TDD, mob programming, and applied learning.

### JavaScript track - Treehouse

March 2022 - May 2022 Got introduced to fullStack development.

### Frontend Development Course - Codecademy

October 2021 - March 2022 Covered foundations of frontend.

### Digital Production - Educons University

October 2011 - May 2012 Covered digital audio and video production.

# Electronics technician - Secondary Vocational School Of Electrical Engineering $\mathbf{M}.\mathbf{P}$

September 2000 - Jun 2004 Degree in Electronics

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Full Stack Developer - Applied Technology

Stockholm Sweden / currently employed
Building and optimizing user focused websites and
applications. Working within a team, developing
and expanding the knowledge with new technologies.

### Inbound Specialist - Brightstar Corp

Stockholm Sweden / Jun 2017 - Nov 2020
Was in direct contact with Telenor's supply chain managers taking care of IMEI/serial number databases and their synchronization between Brightstar's and Telenor's systems. Was preparing device launches.

### Content Creator/Producer/Dj - Radio As FM

Novi Sad Serbia / May 2004 - Nov 2016 Produced commercials, songs and instrumentals. Started and runned multiple radio shows. Has been one of most wanted DJs in the region. Had multiple artist projects and worked with and was supported by many great music industry names.